翻译/压制/字幕制作：HAF半个水果
使用AI工具翻译，如有不准确的地方请在弹幕或评论区指正，谢谢！
So this is going to be a short video of
这是一个简短的视频
what I think is the most obscene thing Microsoft has done yet
讲述我认为微软迄今为止做过的最令人发指的事情
翻译质量权威评价：原来25年就有小拉即用机翻糊弄人了
I've been experimenting on the latest build of Windows for a couple days
我已经在最新版本的Windows上测试了好几天
as the insiders broke the news about the new rejuvenated blue screen of death
因为内测用户们爆料了关于新版蓝屏死机的消息
For one thing it's black again but nothing comes
首先，它又变黑了，但与我刚刚发现的一切相比
close to what I've discovered just now
这些都算不了什么
Everybody's talking about the beta branch where Microsoft released the build 26120.3653
大家都在讨论微软发布的26120.3653版本测试分支
and the exclusion of the bypass NRO script
以及绕过NRO脚本被移除的事
I decided to dig a little deeper and I selected the dev branch and promptly updated to the newer build 26200.5516
我决定再深入探究一下，于是选择了开发分支并更新至较新的版本26200.5516
because I couldn't enable the new version of the bug check on the beta build as stated in the previous video
因为我在测试版中无法按照之前视频所说的启用新版本的错误检查功能
So I enabled the new bug check feature using Vive tool on this version And what do you think I found Watch
于是我在这版本上用Vive工具开启了新错误检查功能。你猜我发现了什么，看好了
They put an ad for one drive in the bug check
他们将 OneDrive 的广告放在错误检查的画面
A blue screen of death that's now green contains an ad
之前的蓝屏现在变成带广告的绿屏
Microsoft what the hell are you doing
微软又发什么抽 (`へ´≠)
This is actually a new low What lobotomized loser decided having an ad in a bug check is a good idea
这真是刷新了下限，是哪个脑残的失败者觉得在错误检查里插广告是个好主意
I'm equally astonished and disgusted by this
对此我既震惊又厌恶
What the hell Microsoft?
说你呢微软 (`д´)
Okay let's freeze frame and read this
好的，让我们停在这个画面，看一下是什么
Get the best deal on your cloud storage with Microsoft 365
用 Microsoft 365 享云端存储最优价
Never lose your work again as your documents save automatically to the cloud
从此无惧丢失工作成果，文档自动同步云端更安心
Plus enjoy one tabyte of storage and the full Office suit
另享1TB存储+完整Office套件
All for just $6.99 a month with your Office 365 subscription
仅需每月$6.99，Office 365订阅全包含
And there's a QR code Well let let me scan
这有个二维码，扫扫看有什么
OneDrive.com All right dude just this is crazy
OneDrive.com 好吧，这太疯狂了
So yeah this is this is a thing Microsoft put an ad in a blue screen of death
没错，微软在蓝屏死机画面里植入了广告
There's nothing that can surprise me anymore And apparently there is a new
已经没有什么能让我感到惊讶了，显然现在还得设置一个新的
registry value you have to set to disable the ad on debug check
注册表值才能禁用调试检查中的广告
So you have to go ahead and open the registry editor
所以你得打开注册表编辑器
Then you have to navigate to
导航到
inside of here you have to create two values
在这里你需要创建两个值
The first one is a DWORD called DisplayParameters
第一个是一个名为DisplayParameters的DWORD值
Then you have to set it to four
将它设为4
Next you have to create another one
再建另一个
another DWORD called DisablePromo
另一个叫做DisablePromo的DWORD值
And then you have to set it to one
将它设为1
And this way the ad is never going to be shown again
这样广告就不会显示了
So let's go ahead and try that out We have to reboot first though
那我们继续试试看吧，不过得先重启一下系统
So shut down
关个机
All right
好的
I forgot it doesn't accept the arguments Great
我忘了它不接受这样的参数 好的
Let's use the command prompt then
那用命令提示符吧
Okay we're back in the system So let's go ahead and check this out
好的，我们回到了系统里，继续往下看吧
Once we crash we shouldn't see the ad anymore All right
一旦崩溃，我们就不会再看到广告了
Honestly this is pretty baffling but somewhat expected from Microsoft
说实话这挺让人困惑的，不过是微软的话也算是意料之中
Once there's extra space on the bug check of course it's going to be filled with an advertisement despicable
一旦错误检查页面上有多余的空间，它肯定会被可鄙的广告填满
I wonder though why exactly the new display parameters are four and one
不过我想知道为什么新的显示参数是4和1
I guess that's just another arbitrary bit mask value from Microsoft
我猜那不过是微软又一个随意的位掩码值罢了
原标题：They Put an Ad into the Blue Screen of Death 原作者：Enderman
Thanks for watching I'm really disappointed I might actually make the move to Linux now Take care
感谢观看，我真的很失望，现在可能真的要转投Linux了。生活愉快
原视频上传日期：2025年4月1日
在 Youtube 上关注
翻译/压制/字幕制作：HAF半个水果
翻译质量权威评价：原来25年就有小拉即用机翻糊弄人了
向所有字幕制作及相关人员道一声辛苦了 (*ˊᗜˋ*)/ᵗᑋᵃᐢᵏ ᵞᵒᵘ*
感谢字幕组的默默耕耘，你们的每一行字都能让更多人能够跨越语言障碍，享受精彩的内容
字幕制作不易，喜欢的话支持一下我吧！